

## BAGUS ILHAM SANTOSO

## **IT System and Operations**

#### **PROFILE**

Saya sedang mencari kesempatan untuk mengembangkan keterampilan baru sambil memperkuat keterampilan yang saya miliki. Pengalaman saya di bagian IT selama 5 Tahun, Saya bisa bekerja dengan baik atas inisiatif saya sendiri dan sebagai bagian dari tim. Kekuatan utama saya adalah kemampuan Analisa dan Inisiatif yang tinggi untuk menyelesaikan sebuah pekerjaan. Saya mencoba mempelajari sesuatu yang baru dari setiap pengalaman karena saya percaya selalu ada ruang untuk peningkatan diri baik secara pribadi maupun profesional.

#### **EDUCATION**

• STMIK Bani Saleh Kota Bekasi 2019 - 2022

Teknik Komputer - D3 IPK: 3.60 / 4.00

 SMKN 3 Kota Bekasi 2014 - 2017

Teknik Komputer dan Jaringan (TKJ)

#### **CERTIFICATION & TRAINING**

- MTCNA (Mikrotik Certified Network Academy)
- **CCNA 1** (Cisco Certified Networking Academy)
- **NSE 1 & 2** (Network Security Expert)
- Menjadi Google Cloud Engineer (Dicoding)

Server

Design

• Ubuntu Server

• Windows Server

Adobe Illustrator

Adobe XDesign

• Belajar Dasar Google Cloud (Dicoding)

#### **SKILLS**

#### Network

- Mikrotik
- Fortigate
- Cisco

#### **Program & Database**

- HTML & CSS
- PHP
- C/C++
- Bootstrap
- MySQL

## Office

- Word
- Excel Access

# **CONTACT**

Telepon : ilhambagus477@gmail.com

: 0858-9443-9480 **Email** 

Portofolio

https://bagusilhamsantoso.github.io/portofolio/

LinkedIn

https://id.linkedin.com/in/bagus-ilham-santoso-128824163/en

#### WORKING EXPERIENCES

### PT Intikom Berlian Mustika IT System & Operation

On Site PT BCA Digital | Mar 2022 - Nov 2022 Job Description:

- Create and Manage User Account and Computer Hostname in Active Directory
- Deploy and Configure Laptop & Desktop User
- Register and Manage IT Asset
- Support Connection Router Fortigate & VPN Forticlient
- Troubleshooting Software, Hardware, Network and Device Peripheral
- Daily Checklist Server & Hub Room

#### PT Intikom Berlian Mustika - IT Support

On Site PT BCA Tbk. | Apr 2021 - Feb 2022

- Checking product quality Laptop and CPU
- Re-Image OS with standard company
- Install and Update Antivirus Endpoint Security
- Respond to Service Request by ticketing system
- Deploy and Configure Laptop & CPUUser
- Withdrawal of Laptop & CPU Users
- Troubleshooting Software, Hardware, Network
- Register and Manage IT Asset

#### **PT Arhapro**

Staff IT | Sep 2017 - Apr 2021

- Deploy and Config Laptop & CPU User
- Troubleshooting Software, Hardware, Network and Device Peripheral
- Manage Database Microsoft Access
- Configure Router Mikrotik
- Planning and Developing Infrastructure Network
- Developing Website Company (Back End & Front End)
- Register and Manage IT Asset